<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paleo Playground</title>
    <link>http://paleo-playground.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paleo Playground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://paleo-playground.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://paleo-playground.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paleo-playground.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-paleo-playground&#34;&gt;About Paleo Playground&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paleo Playground is still very, very early in development.  We have been working hard to bring this game up and develop it into an open-world, multiplayer survival game in which the player takes the role of various herbivorous or carnivorous dinosaurs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What survival elements will be present in Paleo Playground?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Players will need to manage three resources well in order to survive in our ecosystem.  Two of these, food and water, are easily guessable by an audience well-versed in survival games, but the third may come as an interesting surprise.  The third resource that will play a very critical role in a player’s ability to hunt, evade predation, and ultimately survive is comfort.  I’ll go into a bit more detail regarding the roles food, water, and comfort will play in a player’s survival in Paleo Playground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/faq/UI.png&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food will be acquired in one of two ways, depending on which creature you choose to play.  Carnivores will survive solely by feasting upon the corpses of others.  Herbivores will survive solely by feasting upon plant life that’s placed around the map.  Omnivores will survive by eating from both sources, but will only be able to fully satiate their hunger by feeding on both sources of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Larger creature carcasses yield more food value, and larger creatures also require more food to sustain themselves.  This is, in fact, one way we will balance the ecosystem for meat-eaters.  Smaller creatures will simply have an easier time feeding.  The AI in our game will be small, offering less than a bite to a large carnivore.  This means that while a smaller creature such as a Compsognathus may be able to survive solely off the pickings of our AI or a quick snack from a nearby carcass, a larger creature will need to hunt and kill other players to survive.  If everybody wishes to play a Tyrannosaurus Rex, they’ll need to kill each other for survival, as the baseline ecosystem will fail to offer food for such a collection of large beasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding plant material, it works in a similar way.  Large herbivores will require a lot of plants to survive, larger ones being capable of consuming entire areas of plant material at once.  Different herbivores will also eat from different plant groups, with larger ones being capable of eating larger foliage.  The plant life on the map will be tuned such that it poses threat of exhaustion should too many players play as large herbivores.  Plants will regenerate over time, and this foliage regeneration rate is fixed.  A player may find themselves much more relaxed regarding dietary requirements playing a smaller herbivore capable of sustaining itself purely on smaller, quickly respawning plants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have an interesting take on how water works in Paleo Playground.  Our water sources are not static.  They deplete and the water table drops when used for drinking, and it slowly replenish over time.  Larger creatures deplete water rapidly, whereas smaller creatures do little to drop the level of a watering hole.  Again this offers a second check on our ecosystem in Paleo Playground.  If every player wishes to play a large herbivore or carnivore, they’re going to be thirsty and watering holes will dry up, forcing competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the resource that may play the most pivotal role in shaping the player-built ecosystems Paleo Playground will harbor is comfort.  Comfort is a representation of how comfortable you are as a creature in the world.  Stressful scenarios will decrease your comfort, whereas scenarios that provide safety or soothing will yield an increase in comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does comfort work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, comfort only modifies how fast you gain or lose health, however it will likely also influence other factors that govern combat performance such as stamina and ability power, and may even govern rates a player loses thirst and hunger over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have created a simulation below on how comfort effects the rate at which you gain or lose health, though this is a very fickle numerical balance that may change during development.  On this graph are eleven different comfort levels, being 0%, 10%, 20%, all the way up to full comfort, or 100%.  At very low levels of comfort, the player will start dying from stress.  This will happen over the course of several minutes as to not become a detriment in the heat of combat, defense, or hunting scenarios.  High levels of comfort increase the rate you regenerate health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/about/ComfortSim.png&#34; width=1000&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 15 minutes in this simulation, the player has run out of water.  With high levels of comfort, one can thwart dehydration for nearly 15 additional minutes of having zero water.  With average levels of comfort around 50%, dehydration poses an immediate threat to survival.  The same scenario would be present for starvation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does all this mean?  The bottom line is, if you&amp;rsquo;re comfortable and under little stress, you will be better equipped to heal wounds, fight off predators, hunt prey, and ultimately survive.  Stress reduces your ability to survive and, when experienced in high levels, will actually start killing you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be many ways to gain and lose comfort in Paleo Playground.  The most prominent feature of this system is a means to control herds and player association.  If, for example, you are playing as a parasaurolophus, the presence of an acrocanthosaurus will stress you out.  The reverse is also true, and the presence of a herbivore such as a parasaurolophus will also apply stress to the acrocanthosaurus.  These creatures are meant to have a predator-prey relationship in our ecosystem, and thus close proximity will slowly erode a players comfort level.  If a herd of parasaurolophus want to adopt a carnivore into their herd, that carnivore will die from stress and apply a negative, stressing aura on the herd while it does so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Positive proximity-based influences will also be present with the comfort system.  There will be three varieties of creatures when it comes to comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first is herding creatures that will gain comfort when in proximity to others of a herd.  It is likely all herbivores will gain comfort when in proximity to one another, though it is still up for debate whether some herbivores will stress one another out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smaller carnivores will gain comfort from being close in proximity to others of their own kind.  An example of this would be the velociraptor, who gains comfort simply by being close to other velociraptors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last are larger carnivores such as our acrocanthosaurus.  It will only be able to pair bond with the comfort system, in which being close to one other member of its species increases comfort, but any more will reduce comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ultimate goal of this system is to provide a game mechanic that is a check on large, mixed species groups that I forsee forming in the absence of such a mechanic.  The effects of the system will be tuned such that it&amp;rsquo;s discouraging enough to prevent such groups and the tricky part will be allowing differentiation between what&amp;rsquo;s a hunt, and what&amp;rsquo;s not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What kinds of maps will there be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a fan of bright, sunny, tropical maps and I also like islands and jungle ruins.  The map we&amp;rsquo;re currently working on is, expectedly, a bright sunny tropical island!  For a while during contruction of the game in its earliest stages, we played on Tropical_Island_1_MP.  This map used some placeholder texture assets and a low-poly foliage pack I purchased off the UE4 marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beginning March 16th, however, we have began development on an improved map that will likely serve as one of many playable maps in the game&amp;rsquo;s future.  This one for the time being has been named Tropical_Island_2_MP.  It is likely a desert-based map with lush oases and scarse water resources will be created.  A plains-based map and a marsh-based map have also been discussed.  Here, however, I&amp;rsquo;ll go into a bit more detail about the map we&amp;rsquo;re currently focused on, Tropical_Island_2_MP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/faq/Map1.jpg&#34; width=600&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/faq/Map2.jpg&#34; width=600&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To not reveal embarassing screenshots of extremely unfinished terrain, I present above two images that give the kind of atmosphere we will be going for on our first official map.  It will be a series of islands covered with lush, tropical vegetation and hidden, ancient ruins.  As to why dinosaurs are occupying the same time period as man-made ruins, hmmm, it may be revealed later in a post about Paleo Playground&amp;rsquo;s backstory!  The ultimate answer is that I love temples and jungles, and wanted a map with them in it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers</title>
      <link>http://paleo-playground.com/devs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paleo-playground.com/devs/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Paleo Playground is being primarily co-developed by both Predatoria and Vipe, two players who really just love gaming so much that we&amp;rsquo;ve set off on a journey to create our own world in which to play in the game of our dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-predatoriaicon-jpg-width-50-predatoria&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/PredatoriaIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt; Predatoria&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/id/Predatoria/&#34; title=&#34;Predatoria&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;Predatoria&lt;/a&gt; is&amp;hellip; oh hey, that&amp;rsquo;s me!  I should talk in first-person here.  I was a long-time veteran carno player on &lt;a href=&#34;http://store.steampowered.com/app/376210/&#34; title=&#34;The Isle&#39;s Steam Page&#34;&gt;The Isle&lt;/a&gt; and in great part, my great experiences in this game sparked the idea for me to become the founder of Paleo Playground.  I don&amp;rsquo;t have any fancy credentials.  I&amp;rsquo;ve just always been a gamer who, in particular, loves PvP and loves a good fight.  You can see some of my antics &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCmYBMJFBBYgMOLPystoqMyA&#34; title=&#34;Predatoria&#39;s Youtube Channel&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-vipeicon-jpg-width-50-vipe&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/VipeIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt; Vipe&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/id/Vipe_lc_cfx/&#34; title=&#34;Vipe&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;Vipe&lt;/a&gt; is an aspiring digital artist with a passion for paleontology and dinosaurs, and has done some wonderful &lt;a href=&#34;http://thy-vipe.deviantart.com/&#34; title=&#34;Vipe&#39;s Deviantart&#34;&gt;art&lt;/a&gt;.  He&amp;rsquo;s a veteran player of Primal Carnage (Original) and has a particular liking for playing the Pteranodon.  Needless to say, he can&amp;rsquo;t wait to implement our Pteranodon into Paleo Playground!  He&amp;rsquo;s also the owner and admin of the PC server &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1owuv0oIPO-FXLJcQUBbB0pGlxQr9_Qjbntt2IuhHBjE/edit&#34; title=&#34;Server Info&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get your Claws and Guns out!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aren&amp;rsquo;t alone on this endeavor, however.  Many people have stepped up and helped us greatly along our journey to create Paleo Playground.  I&amp;rsquo;d like to give a&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;special-thanks-to&#34;&gt;Special Thanks to:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-bananabaeicon-jpg-width-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/BananaBaeIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198196685093/&#34; title=&#34;BananaBae&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;BananaBae&lt;/a&gt; is a friend and an &lt;a href=&#34;https://bananasareappealing.tumblr.com/&#34; title=&#34;BananaBae&#39;s Tumblr&#34;&gt;artist&lt;/a&gt; who has been supporting us since day one.  She&amp;rsquo;s created loads of awesome concept art including our &lt;a href=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/PaleoPlaygroundIcon.png&#34; title=&#34;Logo Image&#34;&gt;logo&lt;/a&gt; and a lot of our icons on this page!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-hungryeyeicon-jpg-width-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/HungryEyeIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198115008699/&#34; title=&#34;HungryEye&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;HungryEye&lt;/a&gt; is a friend and specializes in creating sounds and audio.  He&amp;rsquo;s supported us by creating several sounds for our Acrocanthosaurus as well as creating our title screen music!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-omnomnomnivoreicon-jpg-width-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/OmnomnomnivoreIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198124262389/&#34; title=&#34;Omnomnomnivore&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;Omnomnomnivore&lt;/a&gt; is another friend and &lt;a href=&#34;http://eclipseadamah.deviantart.com/&#34; title=&#34;Omnomnomnivore&#39;s Deviantart&#34;&gt;artist&lt;/a&gt; who&amp;rsquo;s supported Paleo Playground.  She created our first custom &lt;a href=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/ParaSkin.png&#34; title=&#34;Para Skin&#34;&gt;Parasaurolophus skin&lt;/a&gt;, and has been dabbling in modeling lately!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-sinopiaicon-jpg-width-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/SinopiaIcon.jpg&#34; width=50&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198166827219/&#34; title=&#34;Sinopia&#39;s Steam page&#34;&gt;Sinopia&lt;/a&gt; is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCOVyCg4zDifJPgkgukronGw&#34; title=&#34;Sinopia&#39;s Youtube channel&#34;&gt;godess&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href=&#34;http://store.steampowered.com/app/274940/&#34; title=&#34;Depth&#39;s Steam Page&#34;&gt;Depth&lt;/a&gt;.  She&amp;rsquo;s a buddy I met while playing &lt;a href=&#34;http://store.steampowered.com/app/376210/&#34; title=&#34;The Isle&#39;s Steam Page&#34;&gt;The Isle&lt;/a&gt; and is a mindblowingly fantastic PvPer.  She has been supporting Paleo Playground, and created our first &lt;a href=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/AcroSkin.png&#34; title=&#34;Acro Skin&#34;&gt;Acrocanthosaurus skin&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;img-src-img-devs-synopsisicon-png-width-50&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/SynopsisIcon.png&#34; width=50&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198263149243/&#34; title=&#34;Synopsis&#39; Steam page&#34;&gt;Synopsis&lt;/a&gt; is a friend and an indie developer himself!  He&amp;rsquo;s the lead developer on &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/8AAHgsd&#34; title=&#34;Primal Instincts Discord&#34;&gt;Primal Instincts&lt;/a&gt; and created our &lt;a href=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/devs/Carcass.png&#34; title=&#34;Carcass Image&#34;&gt;carcass model&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://paleo-playground.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paleo-playground.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Paleo Playground?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paleo Playground is the beginning of an open-world, multiplayer-based, Mesozoic ecosystem where players can take the role of several creatures of their choice and attempt to survive.  The ecosystem will be comprised primarily of players, though smaller, AI-based prey will also serve some sustenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is Paleo Playground in its development?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paleo Playground is still very early into its development, which began on January 16th, 2017.  Two months in, however, we&amp;rsquo;re quite proud of what we have to show so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What creatures are planned to be playable?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We currently plan to implement the following list of prehistoric creatures.  In the future, this list is likely to expand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acrocanthosaurus - Ingame&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ankylosaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apatosaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compsognathus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elasmosaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gallimimus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mosasaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pachycephalosaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parasaurolophus - Ingame&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pteranodon - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stegosaurus - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Triceratops - Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tyrannosaurus -Planned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utahraptor - Ingame, but model is being replaced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Velociraptor - Ingame&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will Paleo Playground have singleplayer support, or will it strictly be a multiplayer game?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paleo Playground is being created as a multiplayer game.  We will, however, allow players to host unlisted servers if they desire such that they&amp;rsquo;re effectively solo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What platforms will Paleo Playground be available on?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently while Paleo Playground is in its earliest stages of development, it will only have Windows support.  In the future, MAC support will be added as well.  Steam is our target platform for distribution, but we&amp;rsquo;re a bit early in development to be considering Steam Greenlight yet.  We&amp;rsquo;ll get there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When will Paleo Playground be released?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth be told, we aren&amp;rsquo;t sure yet.  Development began on Paleo Playground on January 16th, 2017, so as I am writing this the game is about 2 months old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will there be Steam achievements?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes!  I absolutely plan for achievements to be part of the game!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much will Paleo Playground Cost?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A price has not yet been decided, but it&amp;rsquo;ll likely be $20-25 on Steam when we feel it&amp;rsquo;s ready to go into Steam-based early access development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can I keep up with Paleo Playground&amp;rsquo;s development?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way to keep up with development is to join our Discord or check the development blog located on this webpage.  Currently, most activity takes place here including links to our most recent test builds and patch notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/xGJznn5&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/xGJznn5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about in-depth game mechanics and descriptions, see the About section!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://paleo-playground.com/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paleo-playground.com/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;here-are-a-few-screenshots-from-some-of-our-multiplayer-open-server-events&#34;&gt;Here are a few screenshots from some of our multiplayer open-server events!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hunting the Parasaurolophus
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/Hunting Para.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deforesting the Island
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/ParaOnIsland.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy raptors
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/HappyRaptors.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A green camo raptor skin
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/Green Raptor.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Exploring the unfinished regions of the map
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/SS1.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An acro is hiding here!
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/AcroCamo.png&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sandy acro
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/SandyAcro.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harassing the AI raptors
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/HarassingAI.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And some screenshots from the older map, Tropical_Island_1_MP&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skin Contest
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/SkinContest.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parasaurolophus Herd
&lt;img src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/ParaHerd.jpg&#34; width=300&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And last&amp;hellip;. There&amp;rsquo;s a bit of story behind this.  I have a &amp;lsquo;debug&amp;rsquo; key that I attach  scripts to whenever I&amp;rsquo;m working on Paleo Playground.  What&amp;rsquo;s attached to the debug key typically pertains to whatever I happen to be working on at the time, and sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s easier to press P than recreate game events to cause a certain part of the game&amp;rsquo;s code to execute during ordinary gameplay.  It just so happens I was working on figuring out a good way for creatures to &amp;lsquo;ragdoll&amp;rsquo; when they ran too fast down a hill in conjunction with our downhill speed-boost system, and forgot to remove a certain script from the P key.  The P key applies physics to the collision capsule that surrounds the dinosaur.  Raptors have a perfectly spherical collision capsule.  This is what happened when raptors pressed the P key:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;420&#34; height=&#34;238&#34; src=&#34;http://paleo-playground.com/img/screenshots/RaptorRolling.webm&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see many more screenshots, I have uploaded lots of them &lt;a href=&#34;http://steamcommunity.com/id/Predatoria/screenshots/?appid=480&#34; title=&#34;Predatoria&#39;s Steam Screenshots&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test post</title>
      <link>http://paleo-playground.com/post/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 16:49:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://paleo-playground.com/post/test-post/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-test-post-markdown-cheatsheet&#34;&gt;My test post. Markdown cheatsheet:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;h1&#34;&gt;H1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;h2&#34;&gt;H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;h3&#34;&gt;H3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;h4&#34;&gt;H4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;h5&#34;&gt;H5&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&#34;h6&#34;&gt;H6&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, for H1 and H2, an underline-ish style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;alt-h1&#34;&gt;Alt-H1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;alt-h2&#34;&gt;Alt-H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;fonts&#34;&gt;Fonts&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Italics *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_ Italics _&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** Bold **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;lists&#34;&gt;Lists&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First ordered list item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another item

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unordered sub-list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual numbers don&amp;rsquo;t matter, just that it&amp;rsquo;s a number

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ordered sub-list&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And another item.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can have properly indented paragraphs within list items. Notice the blank line above, and the leading spaces (at least one, but we&amp;rsquo;ll use three here to also align the raw Markdown).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To have a line break without a paragraph, you will need to use two trailing spaces.&lt;br /&gt;
   Note that this line is separate, but within the same paragraph.&lt;br /&gt;
   (This is contrary to the typical GFM line break behaviour, where trailing spaces are not required.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unordered list can use asterisks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or minuses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or pluses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an inline-style link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34; title=&#34;Google&#39;s Homepage&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an inline-style link with title&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mozilla.org&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a reference-style link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../blob/master/LICENSE&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a relative reference to a repository file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://slashdot.org&#34;&gt;You can use numbers for reference-style link definitions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or leave it empty and use the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com&#34;&gt;link text itself&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;URLs and URLs in angle brackets will automatically get turned into links.
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.example.com&#34;&gt;http://www.example.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.example.com&#34;&gt;http://www.example.com&lt;/a&gt; and sometimes
example.com (but not on Github, for example).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some text to show that the reference links can follow later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;images&#34;&gt;Images&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a logo (hover to see the title text):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inline-style:
&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/raw/master/src/common/images/icon48.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34; title=&#34;Logo Title Text 1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reference-style:
&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/raw/master/src/common/images/icon48.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34; title=&#34;Logo Title Text 2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;code-highlighting-wow&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting, wow.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-javascript&#34;&gt;var s = &amp;quot;JavaScript syntax highlighting&amp;quot;;
alert(s);
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;s = &amp;quot;Python syntax highlighting&amp;quot;
print s
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;No language indicated, so no syntax highlighting. 
But let&#39;s throw in a &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;tag&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;tables&#34;&gt;Tables&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colons can be used to align columns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Tables&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Are&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;Cool&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;col 3 is&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;right-aligned&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;$1600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;col 2 is&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;centered&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;$12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;zebra stripes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;are neat&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;right&#34;&gt;$1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be at least 3 dashes separating each header cell.
The outer pipes (|) are optional, and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to make the
raw Markdown line up prettily. You can also use inline Markdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Markdown&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Less&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Pretty&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Still&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;code&gt;renders&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nicely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;

&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;line-breaks-and-rules&#34;&gt;Line breaks and Rules&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three or more&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hyphens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asterisks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underscores&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>